Guide to the Cornelius Eady Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Cornelius Eady Hosts Robert Bly, interview for Howard County Poetry and Literature Society; an edition of The Writing Life, 1997 June 23; 1 (Box 38)
- Reading at Blue Ridge Community College, Weyer's Cave, VA, circa 1996; 1 (Box 38)
- "Off the Page" Video Poetry Magazine, 1991; 1 (Box 38)
- Cornelius Eady with Carol Frost (probably Boston), 1986; 1 (Box 39)
- Cornelius Eady reading/interview, unknown location, undated; 1 (Box 39)
- Words to Live By, reading for "Our Voices" show, 1995 June 8; 1 (Box 39)
- Live production of "Running Man", 1998 July 2; 1 (Box 39)
- "Fangs", excerpts (probably recorded at City College), undated; 2 compact discs (Box 40)
- Excerpts from "Running Man" at Prince Theatre, Philadelphia, 1999 October 6; 2 compact discs (Box 40)
- Cornelius Eady original songs, 1970-2012; 3; 12 compact discs (Box 40)
- Fangs, New York City Opera Performance, and Brutal Imagination readthrough, circa 2003; 2 compact discs (Box 40)
- Family and friends letters, 1980's (Box 32)
- Letters from literary friends, 1980's (Box 32)
- Literary magazines, 1975-1980's (Box 33)
- "Writer's Cramp", 1984 (Box 33)
- Newspaper articles and fliers, 1979-1987 (Box 33)
- "The Outrageous Color Monster", circa 1977 (Box 33)
- "Victims of the Latest Dance Craze", 1985 (Box 33)
- "Kid mischief," and "Intellectual Honey Pot", undated (Box 33)
- Printed material, 1976, undated (Box 33)
- Poems, 1987-1988 (Box 33)
- Printed material, correspondence, and poems, 1990-1993; 6 (Box 33)
- Promotional posters, 1985-1986, undated (Box 36 (Oversize))
- Printed material, correspondence, and writings, 1990-2010; 10 (Box 34)
- "O Western Wind", undated (Box 34)
- "Victims of the Latest Dance Craze", 1985 (Box 34)
- Materials relating to the Harriet Monroe Poetry Institute's Poetry in New Media Project, 2009; 3 (Box 35)
- Correspondence, 2005-2010; 5 (Box 35)
- Papers Removed from Cave Canem Records
  Papers under this heading were accompanied by a note "For Cornelius Eady's Archive"
  - Clippings, 1996-2002 (Box 35)
  - Reading at Old Dominion University, 1980 (Box 42 (Oversize))
- Restricted Material (Student evaluations) (Box 41)
  Restricted until 2094. For further information consult the appropriate curator.